# Lara DeStein

laradestein13@gmail.com | Portland, OR | (925) 819-1194

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/lara-destein-6353bb149/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/lara-destein-6353bb149/</a>
Portfolio: <a href="https://lara-destein13.github.io/20-react-portfolio/">https://lara-destein13.github.io/20-react-portfolio/</a>

Github: <a href="https://github.com/lara-destein13">https://github.com/lara-destein13</a>

#### **SUMMARY**

Recent graduate of Vanderbilt University's Web Development Bootcamp seeks front end web development position. History of successfully assuming new roles, learning new tools and processes and assuming a leadership position. Promoted three times in less than four years.

### **EDUCATION**

# Vanderbilt University Web Development Bootcamp

Certificate program, August 2021-January 2022

# University of California, Davis

Bachelor of Arts in Psychology, September 2017

#### **PROJECTS**

- 1) My BackYard Trails https://github.com/lara-destein13/my-backyard-trails (HTML, CSS, Javascript)
- 2) Stack Full of Clients <a href="https://github.com/lara-destein13/Stack-Full">https://github.com/lara-destein13/Stack-Full</a> (Express Handlebars, CSS, Javascript, Node.js)
- 3) Stick Ease <a href="https://github.com/lara-destein13/stick-ease">https://github.com/lara-destein13/stick-ease</a> (React, HTML, CSS, Javascript)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Transitional Care Case Management (TCCM) TAR/Billing Manager, East Bay Innovations April 2019 - September 2021 | San Leandro, California

East Bay Innovations empowers individuals with disabilities to live in their own homes, work in jobs of their choosing, and be a part of their community.

Collaborated with government agencies to submit all Treatment Authorization Requests (TARs) and Client Plan of Treatment reports ensuring accuracy and timely submission. Worked to ensure timely payment and to address their questions and concerns. All of this was in service to adults with developmental disabilities we support.

#### **Executive Administrative Assistant. East Bay Innovations**

July 2018 - June 2020 | San Leandro, California

Managed accounts payable and receivable, carefully tracked submission of non-negotiable documentation and informed staff when updated documentation was needed.

## **Community Living Assistant, East Bay Innovations**

October 2017 - May 2019 | San Leandro, CA

Worked directly with clients in their homes addressing their needs on a case-by-case basis. Learned American Sign Language to effectively communicate with a client.

#### REFERENCES

Available upon request